Guide to the Division of Academic Affairs Records RG 6
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series 2. Accreditation
  - National Council for the Accreditation of Teacher Education (NCATE)
    - Institutional Report for NCATE, Volume 1 Institutional Report, April 4-8, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Institutional Report for NCATE, Volume II Exhibits, April 4-8, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 10-12)
  - New England Association of Schools and Colleges (NEASC)
    - New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1953-1955 (Box 9, Folder 37-43)
      Includes - Appendix to Report, Documentary Evidence for Standards
    - Membership Admission, 1954 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
    - Correspondence, 1958, 1973-1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1993, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Re-evaluation Report to the NEASC, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
    - Re-accreditation Report to the Commission on Institutions of Higher Education, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 5-6)
    - Re-evaluation Report by NEASC, March 18-20, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Five-Year Interim Report to NEASC and Supplement, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - A Self-Study and Re-accreditation Report to the Commission on Institutions of Higher Education of the NEASC, Vol. 1, Aug 1983 (Box 3, Folder 9-10)
    - A Self-Study and Re-accreditation Report to the Commission on Institutions of Higher Education of the NEASC, Vol. 2, Aug 1983 (Box 3, Folder 11-12)
    - Institution's Fifth-Year Report for NEASC, Volume One, August 1988 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Appendices for Institution's Fifth-Year Report, Volume Two, August 1988 (Box 10, Folder 5-7)
    - Draft Only; A Preliminary Self-Study and Re-accreditation Report to the Commission on Institutions of Higher Education, NEASC, Vol.1, May 2, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
    - WCSU Self Study Report, October 1993 (Box 3, Folder 15-18)
    - WCSU Self-Study Report October 1993 (Copy to Production 8/13/93), Oct. 1993 (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
    - WCSU Self Evaluation Report, Oct. 17-20, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - WCSU Fifth Year Report for The NEASC, DRAFT 5/11/98, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - WCSU Fifth Year Report for The NEASC, August 1998 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - NEASC Fifth Year Report, Correspondence, Agendas, Minutes, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 13-16)
      2011 accretion. Includes correspondence, minutes, agendas, committee members, and standards.
    - Comprehensive List of Standards and Questions; NEASC/CIHE Standards for Accreditation and Questions Suggested by the NEASC/CIHE Standards for Accreditation, 2001 Revised (Box 10, Folder 16A)
    - Handbook for Self-Study in Preparation for 2003 NEASC Reaccreditation, 2001-2003 (Box 10, Folder 16B)
    - WCSU Self Study, October 2003 (Box 3, Folder 20-21)
    - NEASC Fifth Year Report 2007-2008 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - NEASC 5th Year Report, Steering Committee Organizational Meeting, Oct. 12, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - School of Professional Studies
    - Nursing
      - Report of the Department of Nursing for Accreditation by the National League for Nursing, September 1971 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Report of the Department of Nursing for Accreditation by the National League for Nursing, Supplementary Report, November 1971 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Report of the Department of Nursing for Accreditation by the National League for Nursing, September 1973 (Box 3, Folder 26-29)
      - A Report to the Commission on Collegiate Nursing Education, WCSU Department of Nursing, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Social Work
      - Accreditation and Self-Study Report, Baccalaureate Social Work Program, Vol. I: Narrative, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 30-31)
      - Accreditation and Self-Study Report, Baccalaureate Social Work Program, Vol. II: Appendix, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 32-35)
      - Department of Social Work Self Study, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 36-39)
      - Department of Social Work Self Study, Appendix IV, Student Handbook, Revised July 2003 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Department of Social Work Field Practicum Manual, Appendix V, Revised May 2003 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Department of Social Work Self Study, Appendix VI, Course Syllabi and Supplemental Readings, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 3-5)
      - Department of Social Work Self Study 2004, Appendix VII Documents (Box 4, Folder 6-8)
      - Department of Social Work Self Study 2004, Appendix VIII, Assessment Instruments & Outcome Data (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Council and Graduate Committee minutes, and Matriculation Lists
    - Graduate Committee, 1963-1967 (Binder 1)
    - Graduate Committee, 1971-1980 (Binder 2)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1963-1965 (Binder 3)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1963-1965 (Binder 4)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1965-1967 (Binder 5)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1966-1971 (Binder 6)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1966-1971 (Binder 7)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1967-1969 (Binder 8)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1969-1970 (Binder 9)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1970-1971 (Binder 10)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1971 (Binder 11)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1971-1972 (Binder 12)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1971-1972 (Binder 13)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1971-1972 (Binder 14)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1972-1973 (Binder 15)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1972-1973 (Binder 16)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1973-1974 (Binder 17)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1974-1977 (Binder 18)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1974-1975 (Binder 19)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1976-1979 (Binder 20)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1977-1978 (Binder 21)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1979-1981 (Binder 22)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1981-1983 (Binder 23)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 1983-1987 (Binder 24)
    - Hoburg, Bob Files, ca.1963-1971 (Binder 25)
    - Hoburg, Bob Files, ca.1963-1971 (Binder 26)
    - Matriculation Lists, 1972-1976 (Binder 27)
    - Matriculation Lists, 1975-1979 (Binder 28)
    - Matriculation Lists, 1976-1979 (Binder 29)
    - Matriculation Lists, 1979-1982 (Binder 30)
    - Matriculation Lists, 1980-1985 (Binder 31)
    - Matriculation Lists, 1985-1988 (Binder 32)
    - Unlabeled [Matriculation Lists], 1973-1977 (Binder 33)
    - Unlabeled [Matriculation Lists], 1977-1980 (Binder 34)
    - Unlabeled [Matriculation Lists], 1971-1972 (Binder 35)
    - Unlabeled [Matriculation Lists], 1981-1982 (Binder 36)
  - Sciences
    - Evaluation Questionnaire For Schools Applying For ACS Approval of Their Undergraduate Chemistry Program, Dec. 1, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Series 3. Office of Admissions
  - Accepted Students, 1904-1913 (Box 4, Folder 10-37)
    Includes application forms, letters of inquiry, and letters of recommendation for students. Letters were sent to the president of the Danbury Normal School, John Perkins.
  - Admission Guides, 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 38-39)
  - Admissions Procedures (ca. 1970s), undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Admissions Requirements, September 1925, undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Publications (ca 1930-1969), undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Publications, 1970-1995 (Box 4, Folder 43-48)
  - Publications, 1998-2003 (Box 4, Folder 49-54)
  - Publications (Handbook), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Requirements for Admission, September 1925 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Undergraduate Admissions Form, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Series 4. Office of Institutional Research and Assessment
  - Program Control Data, 1967-1975 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Guide to Grants, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 59-60)
  - Enrollment Projections, 1980-1989 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Admission Reports, 1980-1986 (Box 4, Folder 62-65)
  - Graduate Course Offerings and Enrollment, 1983-1988 (Box 4, Folder 66-67)
  - Student Survey and Results, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - University Enrollment Reports, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 69)
- Series 5. Libraries, Ruth A. Haas and Robert S. Young
  - Annual Report, 1987-1990 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Annual Report, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
  - Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
  - Annual Report, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 6-8)
  - Annual Report, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 9-12)
  - Annual Report, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 40-41)
  - Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 13-16)
  - Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report, 2000- (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Young Annual Report, 1983-2001 (Box 10, Folder 42-44)
  - Archives, Guide to, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Assessment and Vision Statement, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 20-21)
  - Automation, 1988-1995 (Box 5, Folder 22-25)
  - Bylaws of the library faculty, 1987, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Circulation Records, 1919-1976 (Box 5, Folder 27-41)
  - Committees- Bibliographic Database, 1993-1999 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Committees- Library Policy, 1980-1999 (Box 5, Folder 43-46)
  - Committees- Media and Library Services, 1983-1998 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Committees- Public Services, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Committees- Technical Service, 1988-1996 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Connecticut, State of - Connecticut Dept. of Education, Committee of School Librarians, undated, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Connecticut, State of - Governor's Blue Ribbon Commission on the Future of the Library, Final Report, April 1996 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Connecticut, State of - Governor's Conference on Library and Information Services, Conference Recommendations, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Connecticut, State of - Governor's Conference on Library and Information Services, Final Report, May 22-24, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Connecticut, State of - Strategic Plan for Information Technologies, Second Edition, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Connecticut State Library- A Five-Year Strategic Plan (FY1990 to FY1995), Draft (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Connecticut State Library- A Five-Year Strategic Plan (FY1990 to FY1995), 1990 - Advisory Council for Library Planning and Development (ACLPD) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Connecticut State Library- Network Technical Infrastructure Task Force I, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 3-7)
  - Connecticut State Library- Network Technical Infrastructure Task Force II, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 8-10)
  - Connecticut State Library- Connlinet Council, Libraries and Technology in Connecticut; A Report from the Connlinet Council. The Next Five Years., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Connecticut State Library- Connecticut Public Library Statistical Summary 1993-1994, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Connecticut State Library- Long-Range Plan for Library Services in Connecticut 1991-1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Connecticut State Library- Steady Habits and Wooden Nutmegs; Connecticut Libraries in the Year 2000, by Norman D. Stevens, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Connecticut State Library Board - Minutes, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 14a)
    Includes resolution regarding the creation of a WCSU Archives to house deaccessioned materials from the State Library at WCSU.
  - Consuls (Connecticut State University Library System)- Annual Report, July 7, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 15-16)
  - Consuls (Connecticut State University Library System)- Systems Coordinators Meeting Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Consultant, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Director, R. W. Holibaugh, 1991-2007 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Events/Posters, 2000- (Box OS 1, Folder *)
  - Events, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Events/Photographs (23 color w/negatives), April 24, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Events, 2002-2006 (Box 6, Folder 22-26)
  - Events/Mini Digital Video Cassettes (10 cassettes), undated (Box OS 2, Folder *)
    Art Expo, October 29, 2001
    Connecticut Goes to War, Dec. 11, 2002 (1 cassette marked Tape 2)
    Communication Gap, September 29, 2001 (2 cassettes)
    Poetry Reading, April 24, 2001 (2 cassettes)
    WCSU Art Expo, May 7, 2001 (4 cassettes)
  - Geddes, Alfred T., Collection, Certificate of Appreciation, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Handbook, Ruth A. Haas Library (1968-1972), undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Instructional Guides, 1994, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Library Addition and Renovation, Correspondence, 1985-1999 (Box 6, Folder 30-39)
  - Library Addition and Renovation/Move, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 40-43)
  - Library Addition and Renovation, Blueprints, 1992-1999 (Box Map Drawer 5-6, Folder *)
  - Library Addition and Renovation/New Haas Building & Expansion, 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 44-47)
  - Library Addition and Renovation/New Haas Building & Expansion, Blueprints, November 27, 1990 (Box Map Drawer 5-6, Folder *)
  - Library Addition and Renovation/New Haas Building & Expansion, Master Plan/Consultant, 1991-1995 (Box 6, Folder 48-49)
  - Library Addition and Renovation/New Haas Building & Expansion, Publications, 1986-1989 (Box 6, Folder 50-52)
  - Library Addition and Renovation/Swing Space, 1992-1999 (Box 7, Folder 1-9)
  - Library Progress Prints by Galliher and Baier, 1991 (Box Map Drawer 4-5, Folder *)
  - Library Dedication Ceremony, October 17, 2001 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
  - Library Dedication, Clippings, 2001 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
  - Library Faculty Meetings Minutes, 1952-1999 (Box 7, Folder 10-26)
  - Library Guide, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Library Liason, 1995-1998 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Library Staff Meetings, 1950-1952 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Library Pen & Ink Rendering by Don DeStefano, 2000 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
  - Library Statistical Reports-Graphs, 1919-1956 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
  - Library Statistical Reports for Institutions of Higher Education, 1938-1959 (Box 7, Folder 30-32)
  - Miscellaneous, 1946-2001 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - News from the WestConn Libraries, 2003- (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Newsletters, library hours, and clippings, 1960-1982 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Newsletters, Library hours and clippings 1982-2000 (Box 7, Folder 35.1)
  - Newsletters, library hours, and clippings, 2000- (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Niehouse, Oliver L., Collection, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 37-42)
  - Pamphlets, 2000- (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Photographs/Sculptures (17 color and 3 disks), 2002 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Policy and Procedure Committee, 1974-1996 (Box 7, Folder 45-46)
  - Reference Standing Orders, 1994, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Serials List, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Staff Directories, 1987-1999 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Staff Directories, 2000- (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Staff Retreat, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Staffing, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 52-53)
  - Strategic Planning-Library, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Strategic Planning-Library I, 1990-1993 (Box 7, Folder 54-56)
  - Strategic Planning-Library II, 1993-1997 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Strategic Planning-Library, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Student Assistant Guide/Handbook (1970-1975), undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Student Assistant Handbook, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Videotapes, Art Installation, December 10, 2002 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
  - Videotapes, Communication Gap, September 29, 2002 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
  - Videotapes, Connecticut Goes to War, November 11, 2001 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
  - Videotapes, Educational Technology, January 25, 1996 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
  - Videotapes, President William Clinton, September 11, 2000 (3 copies) (Box OS 2, Folder *)
  - Vocal/Piano Opera Scores Inventory (gift), Mar 1989 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Young Book List, 1986-1991 (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
- Series 6. Media Services
  - Annual Reports, 1959-1963 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Audio Visual Program, 1953-1955 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - AVM Shots, Newsletters and Inventories, 1953-1959 (Box 8, Folder 11-13)
  - Catalog of Audio Visual Equipment and Supplies (ca 1937-1959), undated (Box 8, Folder 14-15)
- Series 7. Strategic Planning
  - Academic and Administrative Five Year Computer Plan, Revision, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Academic and Administrative Five Year Computer Plan, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Ancell School of Business, Strategic Plan, July 1, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Appendices for Institution's Fifth Year Report, Vol. Two, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 19-21)
  - Debate Team, WCSU Strategic Plan, 3/17/04 (video tape), 2004 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
  - Five Year Planning Priorities for School of Arts & Sciences, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Organizational Unit Plan, 1992-93 through 1997-98, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Report on Campus Distinctiveness and Collaborations, A Set of Principles for the 1990's, December 1, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 23-24)
  - School of Arts and Sciences, Program/Option Self Assessment, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 25-28)
  - School of Arts and Sciences, Strategic Plan, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 29-32)
  - WCSU Department Assessment Plans, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 46-48)
  - Strategic Plan, All Departments, Draft, March 1996 (Box 8, Folder 33-40)
  - Financial Strategic Plan, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 40a)
  - Strategic Plan for School of Professional Studies, 1992-1997 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Strategic Plan for the Years 1997-2003 (& Beyond), Second Draft, Mar 18, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 42-43)
  - Strategic Planning Workshop, September 15, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Summer Planning Meeting, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - University-Wide Directions & Priorities for 1993-1998 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - University-Wide Directions & Priorities for 1998-2003…and Beyond, Phase II, Draft 2/5/96, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 47-48)
  - University-Wide Directions & Priorities for the Years 1997-2003 (& Beyond), June 3, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 49-50)
  - University-Wide Directions & Priorities for the Years 1997-2003 (& Beyond), Campus Strategic Plan, August 28, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - University-Wide Directions & Priorieties for 1998-2003 and Beyond, Draft 2/5/96 (Box 10, Folder 19-21)
  - WCSU Planning Study, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 52-55)
  - WCSU Program for the Master Plan, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - WCSU Program for the Master Plan, WCSU, Winter 1995/1996 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
  - WCSU Program for the Master Plan, WCSU, Winter 1995/1996 (c.2) (Box OS 1, Folder *)
  - WCSU Strategic Planning, 1991-1996 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - WCSU Strategic Plan 1993-1998 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - WCSU Strategic Plan, 2004-2006 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Series 8. Continuing and Adult Education
  - AACSA (American Association of State Colleges and Universities), 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
  - Adult Recruitment Practices, The ACT National Center for the Advancement Of Educational Practices, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 4-6)
  - CACE (Connecticut Association Continuing Education), 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
  - CSDE (Connecticut State Department of Education), Request for Applications, Vocational Education Grants for Excellence 1988-89, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - CSUS (Connecticut State University System), 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - CSUS Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Course Offerings, 1982-1987 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Course Offerings, "extension offerings", 1973-1988 (Box 9, Folder 13-20)
  - Course offerings - Graduate, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 21-22)
    2008 Accretion
  - Course offerings - Graduate, 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Course offerings - Biology, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Course offerings - Chemistry "advanced", 1973 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Course offerings - Earth Sciences, 1970-1975 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Curriculum Committee Meetings - Sciences, 1971-1977 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - DEC Promotion and Tenure/Budget, 1988-1990 (Box 9, Folder 28-36)
- Series 9. Course Materials
  - Ancell School of Business
    - BBA Program, 2000-2005 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Content includes prososal for elimination of international elective and BBA core revisions.
    - Accounting 105-261, 2001-2007 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Materials include proposals to change prerequisites and course outlines.
    - Accounting 301-341, 2000-2007 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Materials include proposals to change course outlines, prerequisites, programs and proposal sheets.
    - Accounting 361, 2005-2009 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Materials include outlines and prerequisites.
    - Accounting 367, 1985, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Materials include course description and proposal for course deletion.
    - Accounting 402-405, 2001-2010 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Materials include course outlines and proposals for changing prerequisites.
    - Accounting 406-460, 2001-2010 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Materials include course outlines, proposals to establish new courses, and proposals the change prerequisites.
    - Accounting Majors and Minors, 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Materials include proposals for majors and minors.
    - Business (Miscellaneous Courses), circa 1985 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      Materials include information regarding the following courses: Accounting 240 and 241, Finance 285, 385, 346, 387, 390 and 485, Management 385, Information Systems 260, 300, 320, 386m Finance/JLA 318, Finance/Economics 388, and marketing 425.
    - Finance 100-230, 1986-2012 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Materials include course outlines, proposals for deletions of courses and proposals for changing prerequisites.
    - Finance 310-318, 2003-2013 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      Materials include course outlindes, proposals to change prerequisites and proposals to establish new courses.
    - Finance 320-340, 1997-2012 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      Materials include course outlines, course modification proposals and prerequisite proposals.
    - Finance 360-384, 1985-2013 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      Materials include proposals to change course outlines, descriptions and prerequisites.
    - Finance 475-490, 1993-2011 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      Materials include course outlines, curriculum develiopment, and proposed program sheets.
    - Finance Majors, 2005-2008 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      Materials include proposals to modify the Financial Management and the Financial Investments and Markets Finance Major options.
    - JLA 100-260, 1976-2010 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      Materials include course outlines and proposals to modify courses.
    - JLA 300-318, 1976-2004 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      Materials include course outines and proposals to modify courses.
    - JLA 321-329, 1976-1999 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      Material includes course outlines.
    - JLA 330-339, 1976-1995 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      Materials include course outlines.
    - JLA 341-410, 1995-2010 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      Materials include course outines, proposals to modify prerequisites and proposals to establish new courses.
    - JLA Majors/Minors, 1995-2008 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      Materials include program sheet changes.
    - Management 101-251, 1976-1997 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Management 340-355, 1976-2011 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      Materials include course outlines and proposals to change courses.
    - Management 375-406, 1976-2004 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      Material include course outlines and proposals to change courses.
    - Majors/Minors, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      Materials include proposals to change courses.
    - Marketing 235-315, 1976-2013 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      Materials include course descriptions, proposals to modify courses, and proposals to add courses.
    - Management 322-399, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      Materials include course descriptions and proposals to modify courses.
    - Marketing 411-491, 1976-2013 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      Materials include course descriptions, propsoals to modify courses, and proposals to change prerequisites.
    - Marketing Majors/Minors, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      Materials include proposals to modify courses.
    - Information Systems 155-310, 1976-2013 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      Materials include course descriptions, proposals for new courses and proposals to eliminate courses.
    - Information Systems 311-495, 1976-2012 (Box 11, Folder 31)
      Materials include course descriptions, proposals to change courses and proposals to add courses.
    - Information Systems Majors/Minors, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 32)
      Materials include course revisions.
    - Public Administration 200-310, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 33)
      Materials include course descriptions.